<ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Kyle Technology Corp</ENAMEX> said a <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Seattle</ENAMEX> investor has signed a letter of intent to buy the company for about 3 1 million or 1 20 a share The investor <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Donald A Wright</ENAMEX> plans to run the company said a spokesman for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Kyle</ENAMEX> The transaction has been approved by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Kyle s</ENAMEX> board but requires the approval of the company s shareholders <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Kyle</ENAMEX> manufactures electronic components