THE STOCK of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Applied Power Inc</ENAMEX> which split 2 for 1 in May has risen since <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">August</ENAMEX> 1988 In yesterday s edition it was incorrectly stated that the company s share price has softened since <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">August</ENAMEX> 1988 See Who s <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">News</ENAMEX> With One Turnaround Under His Belt Sim Aims for Another at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Barry Wright WSJ Oct</ENAMEX> 17 1989