Vickers PLC a British aerospace defense and automotive conglomerate said it reached an agreed cash bid of 108 2 million 173 3 million for <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ross Catherall Group PLC</ENAMEX> a maker of specialty alloy and ceramics The company said it expects to receive acceptances for its offer of 253 pence 4 05 per share representing at least 67 of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ross Catherall</ENAMEX> s issued share capital or 12 7 million ordinary shares Vickers said its offer also includes an option to receive a redeemable loan note in lieu of cash The notes can be redeemed starting in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">July</ENAMEX> 1991 The company said its acquisition of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ross Catherall</ENAMEX> will be covered largely by cash raised in its <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">July</ENAMEX> disposal of Howson Algraphy for 241 7 million