<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hughes Aircraft Co</ENAMEX> a General Motors Corp unit said the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Intelsat VI</ENAMEX> commercial communications satellite is set to be launched <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Friday</ENAMEX> The satellite built by <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hughes</ENAMEX> for the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">International</ENAMEX> Telecommunications <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Satellite Organization</ENAMEX> is part of a 700 million contract awarded to <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hughes</ENAMEX> in 1982 to develop five of the three ton satellites