A group of investors led by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Giant Group Ltd</ENAMEX> and its chairman <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Burt Sugarman</ENAMEX> said it filed with federal antitrust regulators for clearance to buy more than 50 of the stock of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Inc</ENAMEX> a fast food company based in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Louisville Ky Rally</ENAMEX> s operates and franchises about 160 fast food restaurants throughout the U S The company went public earlier this month offering 1 745 000 shares of common stock at 15 a share <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Giant</ENAMEX> has interests in cement making and newsprint The investor group includes Restaurant Investment Partnership a <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">California</ENAMEX> general partnership and three <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s directors <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr Sugarman James M Trotter III</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">William E Trotter II</ENAMEX> The group currently holds 3 027 330 <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s shares or 45 2 of its commmon shares outstanding <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Giant Group</ENAMEX> owned 22 of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s shares before the initial public offering A second group of three company directors aligned with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s founder <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">James Patterson</ENAMEX> also is seeking control of the fast food chain It is estimated that the Patterson group controls more than 40 of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> s stock <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> officials weren t available to comment late yesterday For the year ended <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">July</ENAMEX> 2 <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rally</ENAMEX> had net income of 2 4 million or 34 cents a share on revenue of 52 9 million