Friday Oct 27 9 p m midnight EDT on PBS PBS air dates and times vary so check local listings <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Show Boat New Jersey</ENAMEX> s Paper Mill Playhouse produced this faithful revival of <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">America</ENAMEX> s most influential musical written by Jerome Kern and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Oscar Hammerstein</ENAMEX> and first produced on <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Broadway</ENAMEX> in 1927 Worth watching although the music has lasted better than the plot or the humor Saturday Oct 28 8 10 p m EDT on HBO repeated Oct 31 Nov 5 8 14 16 and 20 Perfect Witness Aidan Quinn Brian Dennehy and Stockard Channing are excellent in this gripping tale of a reluctant witness in an organized crime prosecution It s set in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">New York</ENAMEX> but it resonates with the terrible dynamics of the Latin American drug wars Sunday Oct 29 8 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">ABC</ENAMEX> The Final Days No doubt there is something to irk everyone in this AT T sponsored dramatization of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bob Woodward</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Carl Bernstein</ENAMEX> s book about Watergate Personally I m irked by its combination of ponderousness and timidity which adds up to an utter lack of drama Sunday Oct 29 10 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on Showtime repeated Nov 2 6 11 and 15 The Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde Fans of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Anthony Andrews Brideshead Revisited</ENAMEX> will relish watching him play the title role s in the 19th century <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Robert Louis Stevenson</ENAMEX> pre Freudian drama of schizoid horror Monday Oct 30 10 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on PBS Journey Into Sleep I promise you will stay awake through this intriguing documentary about the science of sleep Wednesday Nov 1 9 10 30 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">PBS Thomas Hart Benton Critical</ENAMEX> opinion is divided about the success of Benton s populist defiance of modernist art But no one could disagree that Ken Burns has made a fascinating film about this famous American painter Thursday Nov 2 9 10 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on A E repeated at 1 a m and on Nov 5 Third and Oak The <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Pool Hall A</ENAMEX> one acter by the Pulitzer Prize winning playwright <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Marsha Norman</ENAMEX> is the first presentation in a new series called <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">American Playwrights Theater</ENAMEX> sponsored by General Motors <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">James Earl Jones</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Mario Van Peebles</ENAMEX> carry out a bitter intergenerational dialogue between two black men Thursdays Nov 2 23 10 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">PBS Taiwan</ENAMEX> The Other <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">China Judy Woodruff</ENAMEX> hosts this handsome four part series about the history economy culture and politics of the island home of Chinese democracy and capitalism Friday Nov 3 9 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on PBS Our Town Along with Show Boat Great Performances kicks off its new season with this <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Lincoln Center</ENAMEX> production of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Thornton Wilder</ENAMEX> s best known play in which the role of the small town Stage Manager is given a hip twist by performance artist <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Spalding Gray Saturday Nov</ENAMEX> 4 1 30 6 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">NBC Breeder</ENAMEX> s Cup Day Polished hooves fancy turf fat purses the horse race of the year Sunday Nov 5 10 30 a m 1 30 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">ABC New York City Marathon Shiny Nikes</ENAMEX> cracked cement media glory the foot race of the year Sunday Nov 5 8 9 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">TNT Gary Cooper American Life American Legend</ENAMEX> I ve seen a great many moviestar film portraits and this one is outstanding Sundays Nov 5 12 9 10 30 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on PBS Glory Enough for All Can Masterpiece Theatre make a compelling human story out of the discovery of insulin This earthy amusing film answers with a resounding yes Sunday and Monday Nov 5 and 6 9 11 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">NBC Cross</ENAMEX> of Fire The Ku Klux Klan was revived in the 1920s as a national organization aimed at Catholics and Jews as well as blacks One reason for its downfall was the murder trial of D C Stephenson an <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Indiana</ENAMEX> leader whose reckless career is depicted in this film starring Mel Harris thirtysomething and John Heard Tuesday Nov 7 8 9 p m <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">EST</ENAMEX> on PBS Hurricane Has the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">San Francisco</ENAMEX> earthquake caused you to forget Hugo You ll remember when you see the stunning footage taken from inside a hurricane s eye in this edition of <ENAMEX TYPE='untagged'>NOVA</ENAMEX>