Four <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Seasons Hotels Inc</ENAMEX> announced a 2 for 1 stock split and said it plans to increase its annual dividend Separately the hotel chain posted a 13 increase in third quarter earnings to 3 4 million Canadian dollars US 2 89 million or 34 Canadian cents compared with <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 3 million or 31 Canadian cents Revenue for the quarter fell 6 to <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 50 4 million from <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 53 7 million the year earlier The company said it approved an increase in its annual dividend rate to 22 Canadian cents from 19 Canadian cents The dividend will be paid semiannually although pay and record dates haven t yet been determined A company spokeswoman said the stock split planned for Jan 8 is intended to increase trading in the stock On the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Toronto Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> yesterday <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Four Seasons</ENAMEX> gained <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 1 50 to <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 35 75 in light trading The company currently has 7 2 million subordinate voting shares outstanding The company also said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Isadore Sharp</ENAMEX> chairman and president plans to terminate his option to acquire 500 000 shares so they can be distributed to senior executives under a proposed incentive plan In return the company would reimburse <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr Sharp</ENAMEX> in the event of any future sale of control of the company The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Toronto Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> limits the number of options a company can issue to employees The incentive plan is subject to approval by a majority of holders of the subordinate voting shares other than <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr Sharp</ENAMEX> and his associates at a special meeting to be held <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Dec</ENAMEX> 19 The Four Seasons spokeswoman said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr Sharp</ENAMEX> who has an 81 voting stake in the company has no current plans to sell his interest She said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr Sharp</ENAMEX> s stake won t be diluted by the stock split For the first nine months of the year net rose 12 to 9 2 million Canadian dollars or 93 Canadian cents a share compared with <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 8 2 million or 84 Canadian cents a share <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Revenue</ENAMEX> fell to <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 148 million from <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">C</ENAMEX> 162 3 million