<ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Morrison Knudsen Corp</ENAMEX> posted third quarter net income of 7 9 million or 69 cents a share continuing a rebound from steep year ago losses In the third quarter a year earlier the construction and engineering concern posted a loss of 51 2 million or 4 68 a share <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Revenue</ENAMEX> in the latest quarter rose 14 to 589 million from 515 1 million In composite trading on the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">New York Stock Exchange Morrison</ENAMEX> gained 2 25 to 44 125 <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Morrison</ENAMEX> said the engineering and construction segment performed well with the mining and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">MK Ferguson</ENAMEX> operations making important contributions <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Boise Idaho</ENAMEX> based <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Morrison</ENAMEX> had losses totaling 186 million over the two years ended in December but it has surged back to profitability as a result of cost cutting and shedding of unprofitable operations In the nine months the company s net income was 21 5 million or 1 88 a share compared with a year earlier loss of 97 8 million or 8 96 a share <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Revenue</ENAMEX> rose 17 to 1 62 billion from 1 39 billion