<ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">H R BLOCK Inc</ENAMEX> had net income of 100 2 million or 1 90 a share in the fiscal year ended April 30 The figure was incorrectly shown as a net loss in a chart accompanying <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Friday</ENAMEX> s Heard on the Street column See Heard on the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Street H R Block</ENAMEX> s <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Success Story Seems</ENAMEX> to Present a Stumbling <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Block</ENAMEX> to Some Money Managers <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">WSJ Oct</ENAMEX> 20 1989