A unit of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> Partners launched a 10 a share tender offer for the shares outstanding of Dataproducts <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Corp</ENAMEX> and said it would seek to liquidate the computer printer maker as soon as possible even if a merger isn t consummated <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> is controlled by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Crescott Investment</ENAMEX> Associates <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Wilson Investment Group Kernel Corp</ENAMEX> and Catalyst Partners The investor group owns 1 534 600 Dataproducts common shares or a 7 6 stake The offer is based on several conditions including obtaining financing <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> said it had received the reasonable assurance of <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Chase Manhattan Bank N A</ENAMEX> that the financing can be obtained In a filing with the Securities and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Exchange Commission DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> said it expects it will need about 215 million to buy the shares and pay related fees and expenses <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> added that it has not begun discussions with financing sources and said it expected to repay the amounts borrowed through proceeds of the liquidation <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Dataproducts</ENAMEX> officials declined to comment and said they had not yet seen a suit filed in federal court by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> that seeks to nullify a standstill agreement between <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> and Dataproducts Earlier this year <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">DPC Acquisition</ENAMEX> made a 15 a share offer for Dataproducts which the Dataproducts board said it rejected because the 283 7 million offer was not fully financed <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Dataproducts</ENAMEX> has since started a restructuring and has said it is not for sale